<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Exercises on</title><link>/docs/exercises/</link><description>Recent content in Exercises on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/docs/exercises/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tutorial Exercises</title><link>/docs/exercises/ex_intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/exercises/ex_intro/</guid><description>There are three sets of exercises, all on GitHub.
If you are not ready to setup a GitHub account and run workflows, a &amp;rsquo;take-a-look&amp;rsquo; repository with the exercise issues and pull requests is available at take-a-look. You can follow along with the tutorial and read the issues and pull requests without having to run your own GitHub actions.
For those working through the exercises, running the create_exercises workflow will generate the text, python, or Fortran exercises in your fork of the tutorial.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the Exercises</title><link>/docs/exercises/navigating/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/exercises/navigating/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re going to navigate between issues and pull requests using the menu across the top of the repository. I&amp;rsquo;m using the take-a-look repository to demonstrate.
Click on issues to get to the list of issues.
The issues and pull requests are labelled with the language: Text, python, Fortran.
Labels are a way to filter issues and pull requests. Typically on a repository you&amp;rsquo;ll see labels such as &amp;lsquo;Bug&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Enhancement&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Good First Issue&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Examining pull requests</title><link>/docs/exercises/examine-pull/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/exercises/examine-pull/</guid><description>There are a few things to look at when you first approach a pull request. The title of the pull request and the description should give you some information about what the author is proposing.
Next, you can get an idea of how big the pull request is (and how much effort it will take to review!) by looking at:
How many lines of code have been added or removed How many files have been changed How many commits were made These are circled below in pink.</description></item></channel></rss>